export const questionSetOne = [
  {
    question: "React is a _________.",
    answers: [
      "Web development Framework",
      "JavaScript Library",
      "jQuery",
      "Web Server",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which ReactJS function renders HTML to the web page?",
    answers: [
      "render()",
      "ReactDOM.render()",
      "renders()",
      "ReactDOM.renders()",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "JSX stands for _____.",
    answers: ["JSON", "JSON XML", "JavaScript XML", "JavaScript and AngularJS"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: " JSX allows us to write _____.?",
    answers: [
      "jQuery in React",
      "Angular Code in React",
      "MySQL in React",
      "HTML in React",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What are Props?",
    answers: [
      "Props are arguments passed into React components",
      "Props are functions in the ReactJS",
      "Props are used to returns multiple values from the function",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to generate lists?",
    answers: ["map()", "generate()", "new()", "maps()"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
];

export const questionSetTwo = [
  {
    question: "What types of components do we have in ReactJS?",
    answers: [
      "Variable and Const components",
      "Class and Function components",
      "Method and Function components",
      "Array and Object components",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which statement is required to define a class component?",
    answers: [
      "extends React.Components",
      "imports React.Components",
      "extends React.Component",
      "imports React.Component",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Can components be passed as props?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "In ReactJS, what is State??",
    answers: [
      "It's a temporary storage of the elements",
      "It's a state of the execution of the ReactJS application",
      "It's an internal storage of the components",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    answers: [
      "1 Element",
      "More than 1 element, it isn't",
      "React does not return element",
      "None of the mentioned",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following methods is not a part of ReactDOM?",
    answers: [
      "ReactDOM.hydrate()",
      "ReactDOM.destroy()",
      "ReactDOM.createPortal()",
      "All of the mentioned",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
];

export const questionSetThree = [
  {
    question: "In what contintent is Indonesia?",
    answers: ["South America", "Europe", "Asia"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is 64 * 3",
    answers: [186, 192, 197, 400],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many faces does a decahedron have?",
    answers: [8, 10, 12],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What's the capital city of England?",
    answers: ["London", "Paris", "Berlin"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Is JavaScript the same as Java?",
    answers: ["Yes, it is", "No, it isn't"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What month comes after November?",
    answers: ["January", "March", "December"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
];

export const questionSetFour = [
  {
    question: "In what contintent is Indonesia?",
    answers: ["South America", "Europe", "Asia"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is 64 * 3",
    answers: [186, 192, 197, 400],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many faces does a decahedron have?",
    answers: [8, 10, 12],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What's the capital city of England?",
    answers: ["London", "Paris", "Berlin"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Is JavaScript the same as Java?",
    answers: ["Yes, it is", "No, it isn't"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What month comes after November?",
    answers: ["January", "March", "December"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
];
